Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Subjects PE.029
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- T, 1882-2012; 2 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 shared box
  - Transportation: New York Metropolitan Area - Subways Pamphlets and Publications, 1911- (Box 19)
  - Transportation Alternatives, 1990- (Box 19)
  - Trenton Six, 1949 (Box 19, Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire of 1911 I, 1913-2011 (Box 19, Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire of 1911 II, 1913- (Box 19)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire of 1911 III, 1991-2011 (Box 19)
  - Tribute to Activists, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Trieste, 1946 (Box 19)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Trotskyism, 1914-2002 (Box 19, Box Shared Tamiment 006, Folder 2, Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Troy, Jerome -- Disbarment, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Truman Doctrine, 1949- (Box 19)
  - Turkey, 1979-1982 (Box 19, Box 51, Folder 10)
- U, 1905-1999; 3.25 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize flat box
  - Ukraine, 1939- (Box 19)
  - Underground Press I, 1969- (Box 19)
  - Underground Press II, 1969- (Box 19)
  - Unemployed Movement 1930s (Hunger March on Albany, NY, 1934) (Box 20)
  - Unemployed Movement 1930s (Hunger March on Washington DC), 1931 (Box 20)
  - Unemployment I, 1915- (Box 20)
  - Unemployment II, 1915- (Box 20)
  - Unemployment: Great Britain, 1929 (Box 20)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1933-1998 (Box 20, Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Union Busting, 1988- (Box 20)
  - Union Square (New York, N.Y.) I, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Union Square (New York, N.Y.) II, 1980- (Box 20)
  - Union Square (New York, N.Y.) III, 1980- (Box 20)
  - Union Square (New York, N.Y.) IV, 1980- (Box 20)
  - Union Square (New York, N.Y.) V, 1980- (Box 20)
  - Union Square (New York, N.Y.) VI, 1980- (Box 20)
  - Unions, 1905-1999 (Box 51, Folder 12, Box 28, Folder 25)
  - United States Bicentennial, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - United States Civil War -- Black Soldiers, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - United States v. Dennis, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - United States -- Southern States, 1957-1963 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Urban Guerilla Warfare, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
  - Utopias, 1919- (Box 20)
- V, 1940-2002; 3.75 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 2 shared boxes
  - Venezuela, 1967-2002 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Vietnam, 1954-1979 (Box 20, Box 28, Folder 20, Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 5, Box 53, Folder 3-5)
  - Vietnam-China Conflict 1979 (Box 20)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1962-1964 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1966 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, 1971- (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Articles, Essays, and Newspaper Clippings, 1962- (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Brandeis University, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Draft Resistance, 1968, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters, 1962-1966 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters, 1967 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters, 1971- (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters I, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Fliers and Circular Letters II, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: G.I. Resistance, 1969-1970, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Pamphlets and Publications I, 1966- (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Pamphlets and Publications II, 1965-1967 (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Protest Movements, 1963-1975 (Box Shared Tamiment 186, Folder 5-7, Box 28, Folder 21, Box 54, Folder 1-2)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: Trade Unions, 1967-, undated (Box 23)
  - Vietnam War, 1961-1975: United States Government Documents, 1965- (Box 23)
  - Voorhis Act, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Voting Age, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
- W, 1889-2002; 5.25 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 4 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 shared box
  - Wages, 1946-1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Wages / Salary Surveys, 1915- (Box 21)
  - Wages: Minimum Wage New York State I, 1924- (Box 21)
  - Wages: Minimum Wage New York State II, 1924- (Box 21)
  - Wagner Act (National Labor Relations Act), 1939- (Box 21)
  - Wagner, Murray, Dingell Social Security Bill, 1945 (Box 21)
  - Wallace, George -- Shooting, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Warsaw Ghetto, 1944-1948 (Box 21, Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Wartime Prosecutions, 1919- (Box 21)
  - Watergate Conspiracy, 1973 (Box 21, Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Watts Riots, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Welfare, 1971, undated (Box 21, Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Strike (NYC), 1965 (Box 21)
  - West Indies, undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - White Collar Unionism / Organization, 1957-1963 (Box 21)
  - Wire Tapping (Hobbs Bill), undated (Box 21)
  - Wiremen, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Women -- Black Americans, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Women -- Cuba, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Women: Credit, Equal Credit Opportunity Act, 1953- (Box 21)
  - Women: Electoral Politics, 1970s- (Box 21)
  - Women: Feminist Press, 1976- (Box 21)
  - Women: Feminist Retailers, 1990, undated (Box 21)
  - Women: History, undated (Box 21)
  - Women: Labor, 1912- (Box 21)
  - Women: Non-Traditional Jobs I, 1980- (Box 21)
  - Women: Non-Traditional Jobs II, 1980s (Box 21)
  - Women: Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-, undated (Box 21)
  - Women: Suffrage, 1909-1987 (Box 21, Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Women: Television, 1975- (Box 21)
  - Women: USSR, undated (Box 21)
  - Women: Work, 1889-1993 (Box 21, Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Women's Liberation, 1934-2002 (Box 21, Box 28, Folder 22-24, Box 54, Folder 7-8)
  - Women's Liberation I, 1970s (Box 22)
  - Women's Liberation II, 1970s (Box 22)
  - Women's Liberation III, 1970s (Box 22)
  - Women's Liberation: Pamphlets and Publications, 1968- (Box 22)
  - Women's Rights: Germany, undated (Box 22)
  - Women's Strike for Equality, 1970 (Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 6)
  - Workers, 1947-1969 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Workers -- Black Americans, 1972-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Workers' Control, 1948- (Box 22)
  - Workers' Education I, 1923- (Box 22)
  - Workers Education II, 1923- (Box 22)
  - Workers Education III, 1923- (Box 22)
  - Workers Education IV, 1923- (Box 22)
  - Workers Education: Pamphlets and Publications, 1920- (Box 22)
  - Workers Education: Asia, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Workers Education: El Salvador, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Workers Education: Europe (Box 22)
  - Worker's Rights, 1935- (Box 22)
  - Worker's Rights -- Central America, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Worker's Rights -- Haiti, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Working Women, 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1925- (Box 22)
  - Workmen's Compensation: New York, 1935- (Box 22)
  - Workmen's Compensation: Other States, 1910- (Box 23)
  - World Festival of Youth and Students, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1939- (Box 23)
  - World Trade Organization Protests, 1997-2000 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - World War, 1939-1945 -- Opposition Movements, 1935-1940 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - World War, 1939-1945, 1938-1948 (Box 23, Box 55, Folder 6)
  - World War, 1939-1945: Underground Movements - Europe, 1944-1960 (Box 23)
  - World War, 1939-1945: Pamphlets and Publications, 1944- (Box 23)
  - World War 3 Report, 2002- (Box 23)
  - World Youth Festival, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Wounded Knee, 1973 (Box 23)
- Y, 1935-1999; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Yalta Conference, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Yiddish Language, 1997- (Box 23)
  - Youth Movements, 1935-1982 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Yugoslavia, 1940-1999 (Box 23, Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Yugoslavia: Earthquake-Skopje, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Yugoslavia: Pamphlets and Publications I, 1946- (Box 23)
  - Yugoslavia: Pamphlets and Publications II, 1964- (Box 23)
- Z, 1941-1970; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Zambia, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Zimbabwe, 1941 (Box 23)
  - Zionism, 1948-1970 (Box 23, Box 55, Folder 12)